export const questions=[
    {
        id:1,
        question:'What is an E summit?',
        answer:'An E summit is a gathering of aspiring and established entrepreneurs, investors, and business professionals. It provides a platform for networking, learning, and collaboration.',
    },
    {
        id:2,
        question:'Who Should Attend an Entrepreneurship Summit?        ',
        answer:'Anyone interested in entrepreneurship, whether you are a startup founder, aspiring entrepreneur, investor, or business professional, can benefit from attending an entrepreneurship summit.        ',
    },
    {
        id:3,
        question:'When and where is the  E summit?        ',
        answer:'The E summit is going to be organised in campus of our college, JSS Academy of Technical Education, Noida. The summit will be going to happen on (dates can be mentioned afterwards)        ',
    },
    {
        id:4,
        question:'How can I register or buy tickets for an e e summit?        ',
        answer:`you can visit the summit's website, find the registration page, and follow the instructions to sign up and pay the registration fee.     `,
    },
    {
        id:5,
        question:'What is the cost of attending an E summit?',
        answer:'The cost of registration is ( can be mentioned later)        ',
    },
    {
        id:6,
        question:'What are the key benefits of attending an Esummit?        ',
        answer:`Attending a summit can help you gain valuable insights, connect with potential partners or investors, and learn from successful entrepreneurs. It's an opportunity to grow your business knowledge and network. `,
    },
    {
        id:7,
        question:'What types of sessions or workshops are offered at entrepreneurship summits?',
        answer:'This opportunity will offer number of events and workshop including entrepreneurship trends, funding strategies, marketing, innovation, and leadership.         ',
    },
    {
        id:8,
        question:'Who are some notable speakers or panelists at E summits?        ',
        answer:'The notable speakers are .....( Can be added afterwards)        ',
    },
    {
        id:9,
        question:'What is the typical duration of an entrepreneurship summit?        ',
        answer:'The summit will last for 2-3 days.        ',
    },
    {
        id:10,
        question:'How can I stay updated on the latest news and updates about the summit?        ',
        answer:'You may visit our website.',
    },
]